Hurry up!
Come on, let's go!
Go, go!
No! No! No!
- Call it off!
- I can't.
It's doing what you want, so call it off!
You didn't even stop the truck.
My Angie lay dying in a ditch.
I'm sorry about Angela. You know that.
We were...
- Drunk?
- No, I was going to say we were wrong.
We should've stopped.
We should've helped her.
We should've gone to jail for what we done,
but killing us won't bring her back.
- Call it off!
- For Angela.
Well, I'm taking you with me.
Please don't.
All you got was a reprieve, Dallas.
Yeah. One day he'll be coming back,
and there'll be no place you can hide.
There's a price to be paid for doing wrong,
and there ain't no running from it.
I'm cursed for life,
is that what you're saying?
Longer than that.
A whole lot longer than that.
Something queer about that boy.
My boy's just shy, that's all.
Hey.
- Do you wanna dance with me?
- No, thanks.
Come on, I don't bite.
It's just I'm promised to someone else,
that's all.
Yeah, and who's that?
Sorry we're late.
We have a present for the bride.
- You ain't coming in, boys.
- 'Cause we're Hatfields?
We ain't allowed to celebrate
no McCoy wedding,
is that what you're saying?
You McCoys, always thinking
you're better than everyone else.
Yeah.
Not everyone else.
Just you Hatfields.
- Come on, now, Bobby Joe.
- Wait!
Let's see what you got.
Please, Bobby Joe, don't hurt them.
Just 'cause they're idiots, they can't help it.
'Cause you ask so nice, Jodie, okay.
We know we can't go in.
They're just being dumb.
- Hey, hey!
- And drunk.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too, Jodie,
but no Hatfields are allowed.
It's just the way it is.
No offense.
No offense?
Stuck-up McCoys with your fancy weddings.
You're lucky.
Lucky.
Go on home and sleep it off.
What the hell are you doing?
Let them have their wedding.
No McCoy's going to have
a peaceful wedding
as long as there is Hatfields around. Okay?
What did we just do?
- Yeah.
- Distracted the big man, that's all.
Why? What for?
You'll see. Oh, yeah, you'll see.
Yeah, you'll see, Jodie.
Sorry.
Why don't you come and dance with Ricky?
- No, he's weird.
- No.
Ricky, come on,
why don't you dance a bit, huh?
Just dance with her.
Daddy's getting suspicious.
- How about you?
- Forget about it.
Not your sister, dummy. A girl, like a date.
Just dance with her.
I can't.
Your beloved ain't gonna mind.
She ain't even gonna know.
But I'd know.
It'll never work out. You know that, right?
Only if we're dumb enough
to stay around here.
This is home, Ricky. This is where we live.
This is what we know.
You Hatfield sons of bitches. Get out!
Get out!
It's our special day.
Calm down.
Oh, come on, now.
Come on, now.
My cake! Not my cake. Not my cake!
My cake.
No, no, no, no! Stop it, y'all! Stop it!
Oh, no. Oh, not the cake, no.
Come on, get off him.
Not the window!
Boys!
Y'all stop it.
No!
Oh, it's ruined.
Oh, no!
Yeah!
That was great.
Did you see me stick one on his chin?
What the hell did you go and do that for?
We done it for you, Uncle Abner.
To the Hatfields.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Just the stupid feud again.
They attacked a McCoy wedding.
- Where's Daddy?
- Upstairs.
Why, Daddy? Why did you let them do it?
Let them?
Hell, I didn't give no say-so.
They heard about the wedding
and that was it.
- But you could have stopped them.
- Yeah, I could have.
But, Jodie, you just don't know
what them McCoys are like.
So why don't you tell me?
Ain't like I haven't tried,
but you just want to see the best in them.
The McCoys ruined this town.
They stole the best land
and turned it to sand.
Without them, this would be a rich town.
Only good folk.
But they ruined everything.
But folks like us, we got pride.
We don't forget.
You ever ask your Uncle Abner
why he's been stuck in that damn chair
since he was nine?
He wouldn't tell me.
The McCoys were the first family
around these parts to get a motorcar.
They drove it around
as if they owned the town, going hog-wild.
Abner was playing in the road one day
and they hit him with that damn car.
They wrecked both his legs.
Oh.
McCoys were supposed to give us the car
to make amends.
But they were too cheap.
They never handed over.
That's why this feud started.
You going out to see that McCoy boy?
Uncle Abner. I thought you were sleeping.
Well, I ain't as dumb as folks think.
Please don't tell. Please.
You love this boy?
Yes.
So much.
Well, all right, then.
Daddy told me what happened
when you were a boy,
with the motorcar.
It all started with me, sorry to say.
Don't even know
what happened to the damn car.
Nobody does.
All right. You go.
You go and see your boy.
Just be careful.
Thank you.
Where we going, Ricky?
The old well's just here.
Oh, I'm so glad you didn't get hurt.
I can look out for you,
but it's gonna have to be cut a bit short,
after what happened at the wedding.
- I tried to stop them.
- Ain't your fault.
It just means
it's even more dangerous tonight.
Where did she go, old man?
We saw her creeping out.
Just tell us, Uncle Abner,
and we'll let you go.
Don't make us have to bust up your chair.
I can't stand my dad's stares anymore.
Waiting to marry me off to some cousin,
when all we wanna do is be together.
They'll never allow it.
Your father or my father.
Sometimes it seems like
they'd sooner see us dead.
So we leave.
Leave everything? Everyone?
We can't go where they would find us.
They would come after us,
try and drag us back.
Or worse.
- And where would we go?
- Anywhere they can't find us.
But, Ricky, all we know is here.
All I know is
I love you.
Hey, what we got here?
Hey, girl, be quiet now.
Hey, come on, Billy Bob. What you doing?
That's a McCoy.
Still better than a hole in the wall, man.
You're a bad one, Billy Bob.
Grab her wrists, man.
Did you hear something?
Nothing to worry about. We're safe.
We got Sara looking out for us.
Come on, girl, you know you want it.
- I guess we lost her.
- I guess we did.
Let's go.
You no-good, dirty slut.
McCoy, ain't you got no self-respect?
Leave her alone!
You know
what Daddy's gonna do to you, huh?
There's screwing and then there's
screwing around with a McCoy.
- Come on, Jodie. Stop it.
- Let her go!
Get off me. Get off me!
That was mistake number two, boy.
Mistake number one
was dealing with my sister.
- Where's Sara?
- Run away, like you should've done.
Ricky! Let him go!
- No McCoy gets his hands on a Hatfield.
- No!
No!
- No! Ricky!
- Get inside.
No.
- No!
- Yeah.
You want to kill him!
We're just taking him for a ride, that's all.
Here we go.
- Ricky!
- No!
No!
No, no!
Ricky!
No! No!
No!
Sara.
Sara! Sara!
Sara!
Sara.
You're the witch of the woods.
Folks call me that.
I know what you can do, and I need...
I need your help.
The kind of help you can give him
ain't any help at all.
Ed Harley.
Been a while.
Whatever this boy wants,
send him on his way.
We both know what he wants, Ed Harley.
Same thing you wanted.
Yeah, and I'm still paying the price for it.
Don't let him make this mistake.
In the end, it ain't for me to decide.
But I ain't felt a rage like this
since the time you came to me
with your dead boy.
You have to warn him.
Like I tried to warn you.
Let it stay there, in hell, where it belongs.
I already told you, it ain't for me to decide.
A McCoy! How could you?
This stupid feud's
got nothing to do with me.
You're a Hatfield.
Of course it's got to do with you.
It's about some car
nobody even remembers.
It's about being a member of this family.
It's about the McCoys being scum
and ruining this town.
Daddy, I love him.
You never say that to me again.
Never.
- Tommy and Billy Bob nearly killed him.
- Well, maybe they should've done.
You want blood on your hands?
Better that than have McCoy hands
on my daughter!
- And his hands was all over her.
- Shut up!
You go back to your room.
You ain't never gonna see that boy again,
do you hear me?
Never.
You could've left him out there in the woods
where he'd be safe.
Oh, and he would've come back here again.
I told you.
I seen a rage like this before.
It don't drift away.
Please, Haggis, just think on it.
Ain't my place to do that.
If he asks...
Please, just tell him no
and send that boy home.
We'll see.
You're just a gatekeeper, ain't you?
You're gonna be ash.
- In a sack, screaming...
- We all got our curses, Ed Harley.
Now go away, Ed Harley.
I got work to do.
Who you talking to?
Nobody.
Nobody when he was alive,
and he's nobody now.
Where's Sara?
Outside.
Been enough dead things in here already.
Drink.
They killed my sister.
My little sister.
The Hatfields did it.
They killed her, then they tried to kill me
because I love Jodie.
They'll pay for this. I'll get them.
All of them. Every one of them.
They won't get away with this.
I'll make them pay.
What you're asking for has a name.
Pumpkinhead.
Vengeance.
They killed my sister
because of the love I have for Jodie,
and they gotta pay for that.
I can't help loving her.
Even tried to call it off for her sake.
If a day goes by and I ain't seen her,
ain't held her, ain't kissed her,
then it's like the day never came.
I need her. She's everything to me.
And her damn family
won't let us be together.
Now they've killed Sara
and everything's different.
If this is done,
it can't be undone.
The demon will do your bidding
till it's done.
And then you pay the price.
I don't care about the cost.
If you do this, the Hatfields will pay
a terrible price for what they done.
None of them will live to see the end of it.
But you...
You'll pay the worst price of all.
What price?
It's gonna cost you your very soul, boy.
Your very soul.
I can't walk away.
I can't let them get away
with what they've done,
and I need to be with Jodie.
And this is the only way.
Please, you gotta help me.
You can't let them Hatfields
get away with this,
and you can't let them
keep me and Jodie apart.
Raise your hand.
What do you want?
Jodie.
And the rest of the Hatfields?
Dead, gone,
for what they done to Sara, who never
hurt nobody her whole beautiful life.
Your revenge will eat at your soul, boy,
bit by bit.
It ain't easy.
But I'll still love Jodie?
That's all I need.
Mom! Dad!
Mama! Daddy!
- Sara!
- Sara.
Sara!
- Who's there?
- Relax, just here for a drink.
Did you hear something weird just then?
Like an animal.
But no damn animal
I've ever heard around here.
- I didn't hear nothing.
- Too drunk, probably.
Best moonshine in the county.
Yeah, that's the way I like it.
Bear?
Or worse.
Nothing worse than a bear out there.
Don't.
I had a son once,
and it's the only heaven I'll ever know.
He slipped right through my fingers.
No amount of love could save him.
Life is so short.
From one breath to the next.
Who are you?
Ed Harley.
How did you get in here?
Something terrible is happening,
and only you can stop it.
What are you talking about?
Something's been set in motion,
and only you can stop it.
Only you.
We are what we do.
Dolly, why don't you
go get us some lemonade?
Why don't you get it?
'Cause I don't want to see Daddy,
that's why.
Oh, my...
I thought I never would see you again.
They can't keep us apart.
I love you. I'll always love you,
no matter what anybody says
or anybody does.
I thought my idiot brothers
were gonna kill you.
They can't hurt me now.
If they find you here, Ricky...
I've done something
so that we can be together.
Something's been set in motion.
We will be together.
Soon they won't be able to keep us apart.
Ricky, what have you done?
Jodie?
Where are you?
Don't go.
Tell me what you've done.
I love you.
- All right, lead the way.
- It was Jasper who found him.
All torn up, he is,
like a wild animal got to him.
Must've been one hell of a bear.
Have you ever seen this before?
No.
That's a lie.
You seen this before, ain't you?
- You just stay away from me.
- You don't have to be afraid of me, Dallas.
I ain't gonna hurt you.
I'm just here to tell you the truth.
- Truth?
- Yeah.
- This isn't even real.
- I told you five years ago, didn't I?
That this thing would be coming back.
You've run out of time.
Well, there's gotta be something I can do,
somewhere I can go.
You can go straight to hell.
Keep away from Pumpkinhead,
unless you're tired of living.
His enemies are mostly dead.
He's mean and unforgiving.
Hey!
Stop that.
We were just telling her
about Pumpkinhead.
Ain't no such thing.
It's just a story,
something nasty boys
tell nice little girls to scare them.
It ain't real. Now go home.
We was just funning with her.
Didn't look like
she was having so much fun.
You're wrong, though.
Pumpkinhead's real. My daddy said so.
Said he's come from hell.
Just a story.
Folks around here
got too much time on their hands.
Sorry to be the one to tell you,
but there ain't no Pumpkinhead.
Tell that to Ed Harley.
Did you say Ed Harley?
Yeah, he was the one who first called him.
Went up into the woods
and found the witch.
The witch?
Yeah, she lives up there,
about five miles west of here.
- What happened to Ed Harley?
- He killed himself,
but not before Pumpkinhead killed
all those who wronged him.
She was such a sweet girl.
They found another Hatfield,
all burned up by that old still.
They did that for Sara?
Then they had it coming.
If it was a bear, this'll take care of him.
It killed Tommy.
Okay, trap's all set.
We hear him get caught,
then come and watch that bear
trying to chew his own leg off to get away.
I seen it once.
Sat and watched it for maybe an hour.
Tommy was with me that night.
Okay, let's go.
There was nothing
that we could do about it.
He ain't got over the shock of finding her.
What's up, Charlie?
Ain't nothing there.
Charlie, you faggot.
Charlie!
- No, don't go. Don't leave me.
- Hold on.
I can't open it.
- I'm gonna have to cut you free.
- Are you crazy? Cut off my damn leg?
Come on, do it. Do it.
Do it!
Sorry, Billy Bob.
Ricky, what's wrong?
Ricky.
Leave me alone!
What's wrong with you, man?
Ricky, don't leave.
Leave me alone.
Dale, wait.
What the...
Hey. Hey. Hey, boy.
Pumpkinhead. He's real.
I seen him.
He killed my brothers.
He's real.
I saw. It was Pumpkinhead.
Hello?
My name's Jodie Hatfield.
I'm here to talk to you about Ricky McCoy
and Ed Harley.
That boy must really love you,
you being a Hatfield and all.
He ain't gonna kill you.
Like I said, the boy really loves you.
Y'all look like you got bad news.
The four that went out last night
ain't coming back, right?
So was it a bear that got them?
Weren't no bear.
Then it must've been the McCoys.
He wants your whole clan dead
so you can be together,
and for what they done to his sister.
Poor Sara.
She never should have got involved.
Your idiot brothers
should never have killed her.
You don't know that.
Maybe she just fell.
We don't know they did anything.
Ain't gonna get to ask them now.
They're both dead?
And they ain't the only ones.
And you called that thing for him?
You let Ricky sentence my family to death
for something they maybe didn't even do?
It ain't her fault.
She tried to tell him what the cost would be.
But in the end, it ain't her decision.
Ed Harley.
Back again.
Yeah, that's my curse,
and there ain't no end to it.
- You have to call it off.
- Can't.
He stays till the killing is done,
then he goes back.
That's just the way of it.
Ricky, then.
Ricky brought it here. He can call it off.
You're the only one that can stop it, Jodie.
How?
Do you remember what I told you?
We are what we do.
You're gonna have to do
the hardest thing there is.
What does that mean?
You'll know when the time comes.
Tell me. What does he mean?
Means what he says. That's all.
Sorry to be the one to tell you this, Jim.
It's the worst part of the job.
I don't see how a bear
could've got all of them.
They was experienced hunters.
I taught them myself.
It ain't no bear doing this.
Bears just don't go after one family,
and we got six dead men now.
They all got the Hatfield name.
Are you saying the McCoys are doing this
and taking some kind of revenge
for what happened to that little girl?
- Not the McCoys.
- Well, then who?
It's not who, Jim. It's what.
You've heard of Pumpkinhead?
That's just a legend,
one of them campfire tales.
It's real.
Ed Harley started it.
Ed Harley went crazy, killed some kids,
then shot himself.
Everything else were just made-up lies.
He called Pumpkinhead.
Ed Harley never killed no city kids.
The only man Ed ever hurt were himself.
Now, Pumpkinhead's back,
and it's killing your family.
It's got six so far, and if we don't fight back,
it's going to get the rest of you.
You're crazy. You been in the sun too long.
I got six deaths to grieve,
and you come up here with
these old wives' tales and scary stories.
It's real, Jim.
You just gotta ask Jimmy Langford.
It's what Dale told him before he died.
Pumpkinhead attacked him.
Jimmy Langford is a damn drunk
and you're supposed to be the damn sheriff.
- I got no time for this!
- He's telling the truth, Daddy.
I seen it.
It was Ricky who called it.
That McCoy boy you've been messing with?
He blamed Billy Bob and Tommy
for what happened to his sister, Sara,
and he called the demon to kill...
- To kill us all.
- I seen it, Daddy.
It was right in front of me.
And I'm sorry,
but I'm the only one Ricky won't let it kill.
I'm sorry.
Come on, it's payback time.
Brett, what are you doing?
- Getting some payback on the McCoys.
- The McCoys didn't...
Hold up there, now. Whatever you boys
think you're doing, you got it wrong.
We're gonna do what we should've done
years ago, burn them out.
Now, y'all listen to me. You got it wrong.
It's not the McCoys that are killing
your brothers and your cousins.
It's Pumpkinhead.
- Ain't no such thing, Sheriff.
- No, it's real and it's back.
It's just a story.
You're just trying to protect the McCoys.
- Yeah.
- He's telling the truth, Brett!
Only one kind of monster
living around these parts,
and they all got the name McCoy.
We're gonna burn them out once and for all.
Now, I can't let you boys do that.
No. Don't do this.
Don't. Here, guys.
Guys, just listen!
Listen!
Why are you doing this, Brett?
- Leave us.
- Don't!
You're only going to make things worse.
Damn you!
Right.
- He's still our son.
- I don't know where he is.
You saw. He went off into the woods,
told us to leave him alone.
He was upset. What if the Hatfields
get into their dumb heads
that he's the one doing all that killing,
killing all their brothers?
- Boy gotta look after himself.
- He's not like the others.
He's sensitive.
He's not tough like the others.
You can't just leave him all alone
in the woods.
Dad, open up.
- Bunch of Hatfields have pulled up.
- Oh, no.
Damn! What now?
Do it.
Go on.
Wait!
What are you doing? Brett!
Get out of here!
Come on, boys.
You're going to pay for this.
Stop! Stop!
Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Help!
Listen.
- Help!
- Listen.
Listen! Stop it! Stop it. Listen.
Stop it.
- Help me!
- Listen.
- Stop! Everybody, stop it!
- Help!
I'm burning in here!
Mama?
Help me!
Boys, help me!
Somebody help me!
Ricky! Somebody!
Help me!
Get out of the way. Get out of the way!
Help!
Somebody help me!
Help me!
I'm dying!
Somebody help!
Come on.
- Come on. Come on, here.
- Jodie! Jodie, help me.
- Here, put this over your head.
- Please get me down.
Oh, my God!
Quick, Jodie.
I can't.
Then we're both gonna die.
Grab hold.
Get back up there. Jodie's still up there.
- Come on, Jodie!
- Jodie!
Run and jump.
Jump, Jodie.
Now jump.
It's all right, let her down.
Give me your hand. Come on. It's okay.
It's all right. It's all right.
I never seen Daddy so mad.
He said even McCoys don't deserve
what they did.
He's right. It's not their fault.
It's not them who are doing this.
It's Ricky.
Ricky McCoy? The boy you...
The whole thing's more my fault
than the rest of the McCoys.
He did what he did 'cause he wanted us
to be free to be together.
And now six men are dead
and the McCoys lost their house
and a lot more than that,
and all 'cause of me.
What did Ricky do?
What did Ricky do that was so bad?
Called something
that he should've left alone.
Gonna kill an old woman?
Gonna do it in Billy Bob's name?
How about Tommy?
You think he'd be proud?
Well, I'll be.
I ain't here for more trouble.
There's been death on both sides.
We lost our little Sara, our house.
I know you lost more.
Six of our boys.
We don't put a stop to this,
we're all gonna end up in the ground.
Now, this here's the car
that knocked down Abner.
Now it's yours.
I'm calling a truce,
for all our sakes.
So now it's over?
Wish it was that easy.
What do you mean?
Your boy Ricky.
You don't know what he done?
Been acting real strange.
We got a powerful problem.
We gonna need your help.
We are not gonna listen to you! No way.
It ain't gonna happen. Not anymore.
Sit down, Hatfield, and control your boys.
It ain't gonna happen.
Tell me something.
Why don't you shut up over there, all right?
Sit down, Hatfield. Just come here.
Tell them, Papa.
Hatfield, control those boys.
Get them to sit down.
Sit down!
Shut up!
What Ricky done
had nothing to do with the rest of us.
We ain't saying it has,
- but we have to stop this thing.
- But six of us are dead because of him.
- Yeah!
- Sit down.
Six of us are dead.
Come on, shut up. Shut up!
You ought to be in bed.
What are they gonna do?
I don't know. Come on. Back to bed.
- Is the monster going to kill us?
- No.
No way.
I ain't gonna let it get anywhere near you.
But I'm a Hatfield.
Come on, you ought to be sleeping.
I'm going to kill you all.
Finish it.
Kill them all.
...good-for-nothing
and you always have been.
- Shut up, you idiot.
- Yes, you are. Yes, you are.
- Your family's past it.
- You know nothing, none of your family.
This ain't even our problem.
All we gotta do is walk away.
Let that thing kill them Hatfields.
What do we care?
Hey! We got little ones in this house,
you son of a bitch.
You gonna leave them to die, too?
There's only one way to deal with this,
but you McCoys ain't gonna like it.
- I don't care what they like.
- Shut your mouth.
Let's just hear the man.
I know what I'm talking about here.
There ain't no other way.
You gotta trust me on that.
There's no stopping this thing.
You can't kill it, you can't reason with it
and you can't outrun it.
It'll get you soon enough,
and it'll rip you to pieces.
All right. So what do we have to do?
You know who called it?
Ricky McCoy.
Yeah.
The way they say he was acting at the wake,
you gotta say it was him.
It's how they act,
the ones that summon the thing.
It kills,
and they feel it somehow.
See it.
- How come you know so much about this?
- Just trust me, I do.
You're saying
there's something we gotta do?
First thing you gotta do
is find Ricky McCoy.
And once we find him? Then what?
- Then you gotta kill him.
- No. No way.
We're not going to kill our brother.
- Does that mean the monster's coming?
- No.
Just a storm. Normal, harmless storm.
Nothing to be scared of.
Then how come there's thunder
and lightning and no rain?
This ain't no normal storm.
It's coming.
Everybody's here in the house.
We're well protected.
They're just figuring a way
to sort things out.
Can they do it?
Sure they can.
It's Ricky or all of us.
- Yeah, he brought this on himself.
- Look. Ricky done wrong.
- But we ain't going to kill our own brother.
- Then we'll do it.
We're all gonna have to work together.
First you gotta find him.
You're expecting McCoys
to help hunt down one of our own?
We got children in this house.
You're gonna stand by
and let this thing kill them
just to save your brother?
Blood is blood.
We didn't ask for this,
and now we're gonna protect our family.
- Like we're trying to do right now.
- We didn't start this.
Your boys killed our Sara.
Then, yeah, you did.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hold it! Hey, hey!
While you're wasting time
fighting each other,
that thing is still out there.
Long as Ricky McCoy's still alive,
there's no getting away from it.
It'll find you, it'll kill you
and it'll move onto the next.
It'll kill the men. It'll kill the women.
It makes no difference to it.
It'll even kill the children.
It will kill all those who are marked.
It'll also kill anybody
who tries to get in its way.
We're not talking about an animal.
We're not talking about a man.
This is a thing straight from hell,
and it's here to kill a whole family
and anybody else who gets in its way.
This land's gonna be soaking in blood
unless you find and kill Ricky McCoy.
No!
There's gotta be another way.
I'm sorry, Jodie. There ain't no other way.
But he's the man I love.
We couldn't tell any of you
'cause of this stupid feud
and all the bad feeling.
We always had to sneak around
like we were doing something wrong.
But we weren't. I love him and he loves me.
And you can't kill him.
Please.
We'll find another way.
There ain't no other way.
Now, how come you know
so much about this?
Five years ago,
my brother and I were driving around
drunk as skunks one night,
and we hit a woman.
We got scared and drove off.
She died in a ditch beside the road,
probably hours later.
I mean, we could've helped.
We should've helped, but we were too afraid
of what our father was gonna do.
A young man named Andy Mills
found himself
putting his young wife into the ground.
He knows we'd done it,
but he couldn't prove it,
not when our father was the sheriff
and he was keeping things quiet.
So Andy went off into the woods
and he did what Ed Harley had done
before him.
Called on this thing, Pumpkinhead.
And I saw it kill my brother.
And I went to Andy
and I begged him to call it off.
But he couldn't, even if he wanted to.
That thing damn near killed me, too.
How'd you get away from that?
Well, I figured I was gonna die anyway.
I might as well take Andy with me.
And I killed him.
When he died, that thing was gone, too.
And I learnt its secret that night,
and it wasn't something
I was ever gonna forget.
And that's how I know
what you all gotta do now.
Please.
Please don't do this.
Sheriff.
What is it?
I see it. It's coming.
- Do you hear something?
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
- What's happened?
I don't know.
No!
- No, Brett!
- Pull!
Oh, my God! No!
No!
It ain't getting in here, boys. Come on.
Finish it.
- Come on, come on, pass them out.
- There we go.
Tristan.
Little Joe.
Emmett.
Mikey.
Come on, boys. Get up there. Come on.
- Does anybody see it?
- No.
Let's get out of here.
This is the Hatfields' problem.
There ain't nothing we can't do
about that thing.
- You saw it. You all saw it.
- Shut up.
We stay and fight, then we all die, too.
You heard what the Sheriff said.
Everybody trying to protect
the ones it wants gets killed, too.
You ain't gonna leave us.
Come on.
We didn't bring this thing on ourselves.
Look, there ain't nothing we can do,
so what's the point of us staying
and dying, too?
Would you shut up? I can't believe
I'm hearing this from one of my own boys.
It's one of us that did this.
Ricky brought this death down here.
Are we supposed to turn tail and run?
How are we supposed to live with that?
It weren't the Hatfields that called it.
It's one of ours.
We stay and fight
and we try to put right what Ricky's done.
Now, let's kill this thing
and send it back to hell, where it belongs.
Remember what I told you.
Only you can stop it.
- You can save his soul.
- How?
You have to do the hardest thing there is.
It's climbing the walls.
It's on the roof.
Get away from her!
Tristan!
Hey!
Are you hurt? Are you hurt?
Ricky.
It's time, Dallas.
I told you this time would come.
I know.
You have to go out there and face it.
It's gonna kill me.
I told you five years ago
there'd be no place to hide.
Now, you and it
have got some unfinished business.
You gotta finish it.
You face it
and you can make some wrongs right.
I am trying to save you from my fate,
trapped between for all time.
I can't even see my son.
But you...
You can save your soul.
Don't do this!
I ain't gonna sit by and let it kill my family.
My son started this.
This mess started
before your son was even born.
- Stay back.
- What are you doing?
Had five more years than I was supposed to,
but now it's my time.
Ricky. Ricky, you have to stop it. Ricky.
I did what I did
so that we could be together.
Tell it to stop. Please, Ricky. Make it stop!
- Ricky. Ricky.
- I can't.
- Ricky, please. Ricky.
Ricky. Ricky, please.
I killed two people in my life.
I see their faces every time I go to sleep.
Second one was 'cause of you.
That's right. You remember me.
I beat you before.
It cost me. This one's for my brother,
you son of a bitch.
Ricky, listen to me.
Ricky, you have to stop it.
- Listen to what it's doing, Ricky.
- Just stay out of its way.
Ricky.
- Sheriff!
- Jodie.
I don't want it to hurt you,
but if you try and stop it, it will kill you, too.
Smile, you son of a bitch.
Dolly, run!
You're gonna help my sister.
They killed Sara. They started it.
What's done can't be undone.
If you really love me, Ricky McCoy,
then you'll help me now!
You bastard!
No!
Put her down! Not her. Put her down!
Ricky, don't let it hurt her!
Ricky!
Oh, my God. What have I done?
No. This wasn't the deal.
She's just a little girl.
This isn't what I asked for.
You were supposed to make it
so me and Jodie could be together.
This isn't what I wanted!
- Kill me.
- No.
- It's the only way.
I know you can do it.
I know you can do it. It's the only way.
You got no choice.
- I can't shoot you, Ricky.
- Please, Jodie.
I got enough blood on my hands.
No, I can't do it!
I love you.
Do it, Jodie!
No!
Is it gone?
It's over.
There ain't nothing harder
than letting go of someone you love.
We are what we do.
You done good, Jodie.
You done good.